Clash! God vs. Ryoutsu!
Senpai! Senpai!
Please wake up early! You'll be late!
Noisy!
Are you going to wake up soon?
What is that bookshelf?
It was noisy, but I slept well.
What is it, a chicken?
This looks like a chicken!
It's a chicken!
This is an eagle!
Ryoutsu-san! Don't run away!
It's not a chicken!
It's really a chicken
How much is it in grams?
It becomes a side dish for rice.
You can't run away like this!
Even if I do this here, there is no specification.
Let's go to work for now.
Good morning
Ryoutsu!
What time do you think it is?
You have a sense of self-awareness as a full-fledged member of society.
Manager!
Stay tuned
Gyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
What's wrong, Ryotsu! Did you eat something bad?
I thought you were acting like a human for a while now.
I can't believe I'm really no longer human.
Maybe this is a transfer?
Huh? Transferred?
Ryo-chan is always doing bad things
God in heaven punished me
Tell me what wrong I did!
Don't tell me!
That's right! If you're going to complain, you should tell it to God!
Yeah!
That's certainly true
I'm going to heaven for a while
Are you coming?
Do you know where it is?
It's called heaven, so it's up in the sky!
There's no way rockfish can fly, right?
Wow!
It flew away!
It's a rockfish
Does God exist?
If you don't let me see it, I'll be in trouble!
If I leave him alone any longer,
I don't know what to do!
Damn! What is heaven like?
Come on!
tired!
Aaah! I’m going to lose!
Oh! There's no doubt about it! This is heaven!
Yay! Where is God?
Ryochikankishi came to complain!
Hey! Where are you! Where are you! Where are you! Where are you?
Hmm! Well, you ran away before I saw you coming!
For now, let's leave proof that we came here.
Smooth and smooth
This is fine
Hohohohohoho
What is this voice?
god
Is it God? Where is it?
I've been right in front of you ever since.
Holly
Wow!
What do you think? I'm God
Koke!
No, I can't walk on my feet if it's this big.
If you're careless, you might get trampled on.
That's totally annoying
I don't want you to say that
God is omniscient and omnipotent
There is no such thing as carelessness.
That's why I know what you want to say
I turned you into a chicken because you exceeded 20,000 points for bad behavior.
What is the point of that bad behavior?
Points are given to every bad behavior of humans.
1 point for lying
If you do a good job, you get 10 points.
If you exceed 10,000 points in total, you will be sent to hell after death.
And if you exceed 20,000 points
Koke!
It's a rule to become a chicken.
I won't do anything that bad.
sweet sweet
It's written in God's notebook.
Do you think I'll leave it to you?
When you were a baby, you stole the bottle from the baby next to you.
First 12 points
A habitual offender of flipping up skirts in elementary school
122 points now
In junior high school, I played a prank on the principal.
222 points now
Oh
And even after becoming a police officer, I was late.
I don't know how many times I've slacked off.
And yesterday
The taiyaki that Manager Ohara bought.
Hurry up
That's 20,000 abuse points.
Ahhh
Wait a minute
picture?
When I calculated it, it didn't add up to 20,000 points.
no doubt
That's 19995 points.
picture?
I calculated it twice.
Why can't you even say that you're omniscient and omnipotent?
I'm not an idiot
Number 1 means that there will be 5 deaths.
Human Bunzai also used defense.
This crime is serious
35,000 additional abuse points
What are you doing?
Anyone with a total of more than 55,000 points becomes a fly.
It's not dirty.
Bring it back
picture?
This is already
Message from Goddess
picture?
Goddess's message
Well, what's the phone number?
If you're on the phone
Return me to my original form
Bring it back, bring it back, bring it back
Totally annoying fly
Jeez
Bring it back, bring it back, bring it back
Like this
Noisy
Ah, I'm back to being human.
What are you doing here? Let go of me!
People like you who don't even fear God will go to hell and the far east.
He's a god
What would you do if you suddenly threw it and died?
What?
He's a living human being, my king.
what
To be sent to hell alive
That guy is pretty evil.
It's been a long time since someone I've met has arrived.
Who are you?
I am the ruler of hell
King Enma
hell's suffering
It will give you plenty of flavor, human.
Today is a fun date with the goddess
Now, what clothes should I wear?
What?
God it's hard
What on earth is going on?
The forces of hell have invaded heaven
what
But King Enma is not so foolish as to disobey me.
Apparently, there was a revolution in hell recently and a new leader took over.
King Enma
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, guy
Shoot, shoot, shoot
Okay, shoot, shoot, shoot.
I'll show God the power of hell
What does it mean to go to war with God?
After all, this is not an opponent we can win against.
Hey
what are you doing
Yeah?
If you have time in your pocket, just work quietly.
Yes
Utsumi-juku and Yellow River-juku will collapse.
Half of heaven is already a sea of ​​fire.
Did you know, God?
Foolish people, realize the power of God.
gongododanbajitofunenkojoretsushinyo
At the time of underground bridge Ranbu creation Team personnel issues Traffic safety Yakiniku set meal
Underground bridge dance
Mr. Ranbu
Oh, God, you've been so rough.
Eh, even though you're a human, you're surviving well with the current attacks.
Don't think it'll stay like this, God.
Well, you live in a pretty nice place, don't you?
Ah, it smells good
Oh, look at something nice
Let's eat
delicious
Shit, just take a carefree bath
Today I have a date with a goddess
A wig is useful in times like this.
But this is a secret that no one knows about.
If it were found out, God's authority would be disrespected.
Oh, even worse, Goddess will hate me.
Ah, I saw it.
you
I thought it was suspicious that even though he was a god, he had a pants perm.
I'll give everyone the flu
Oh, stop it
Everyone in heaven
God's head is actually
return to ground
It was a dangerous place.
Hey, Senpai, where did you come from?
Oh, oh, is this inside the emission center?
Yay, yay, yay!
I was worried, Ryo-chan.
It's true, I didn't come back for a week.
Hey, Ryotsu, take this as an opportunity to change your attitude in life so you don't become a chicken again.
Hey, it's okay
what's okay
I'll never be a chicken again
because
I hold God's weakness
god's weakness
Yes, only here
In fact, the hair on God's head is
Well, senpai
Ryo-chan
Don't worry, I'm just unconscious
Even if I'm not that surprised
i am god
Ah, you are God
I saw it for the first time
They usually don't come down to the human world.
However, I don't know how much trouble it will cause to those around me if I leave this man alone.
Above all, if the wig was revealed, I would want to live.
Now that I think about it, this guy
Well, I said that I had grasped God's weakness.
I claimed to have grasped God's weakness.
Doki
Hohoho, there's no way God has any weaknesses.
No doubt, this one is definitely
reveal my secret
Well, bad people have to stand up from the ground up.
Extract the root of evil from this man
evil exorcism
You did something unnecessary to me.
Shows things to the eyes
It's money, it's money
Wow, what the hell
I need to do something soon
There's no need to panic.
Humans have an evil heart and a conscience
If you make them fight, conscience will always win.
Come out, conscience.
Um, no reaction at all.
M-money-money
Conscience, come out, conscience, come out, conscience, come out, come out.
Money
Hey, can't you hear me? My conscience, my conscience, my conscience.
Hmm, this guy doesn't seem to have a conscience.
Money
It's money, it's money
The power is amazing because it is a mass of desire.
If you leave it alone, you'll be in trouble.
If this happens, I guess I'll have no choice but to stop it.
Mei, prepare for battle
Come on, I'll be your opponent.
What is this guy trying to do?
Transform
What do you think? Money is well spent.
It's definitely a win
Money
Definitely a win
decided
left straight
What do you think, did you realize that?
Please be sweet
It is said that there is no one who laughs at one yen.
Make sure you have plenty of change, too.
Yeah, it's time to get over it
It's gold after all, it's strong.
What do you think?
I apologize for the inconvenience, I will put the evil spirit out of business and become a conscience.
That's true, okay
Taking what the evil spirits say seriously
After all, it's the money of the world, money.
I'm sorry
God, I have a good idea.
picture?
Hmmmm, I see.
Hey demon, look at that.
Isn't that a money tree?
With this, you don't have to worry about money
Oh!
Yeah!
Fly to the end of the universe
Destroying himself with money was a typical end for him.
Ryo-chan, Ryo-chan!
Huh? I didn't expect this.
Yunto?
Excuse me
alien!
Look at this
Ryo-chan!
Our planet was troubled because of this man.
Our stars are in trouble because of this guy
Please do something about it
Ha, I can't believe I'm causing trouble even if I go to another planet.
It's a stain on the earth, really.
Money, money!